Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you too.
I brought you something.
Okay, I got it.
Oh, my God!
Where are you going?
Oh, but 212?
What kind do you like?
Uh, what? I like the salty kind.
There's a lot of salty ones.
Wow, I like this one a lot.
I like the cheese type a lot.
Mentaiko Garlic French!
Looks delicious!
I don't know what to do, but the green onions look like a lot of Chigasaki!
I love this! The espresso car is full of people and there is only one left!
Hey!
A dog apron and a spec cabaret!
I'm sure it's a supermarket, and it's a bread shop, so it looks like it was made before sweet!
Looks delicious!
I'm not sure I could eat a spy. I'm sure it's a tasty closer.
I'm sure it's a delicious closer.
I'll be right back.
I'm out of here.
I can't wait to try the bread.
I can't wait to try it.
Is that...
You're here?
Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I am Tomomi from Scandal. I am Rei Hoshinami, the lead actress of Shibichi-ebi.
I bought some delicious bread. We'll eat it together later.
Thank you very much. Bon appétit. Thank you very much for your cooperation today.
I'm really looking forward to it. I'm really looking forward to it, but it's raining.
It's raining a little bit. It's a little bit terrible.
I heard it's going to rain 20mm. Twenty millimeters is scary.
I heard there's a really nice driving range.
Let's go there and practice a lot and talk.
You don't get a chance to practice there, do you?
I'd like you to teach me.
By all means, if it's all right with me.
What should I call you, by the way?
I'm Riko.
Riko or Riko-chan?
Riko...
Riko-chan.
Is that okay?
Riko, please.
I'm ...
I'm often called Tomo.
Then may I call you Tomo?
Mirei-chan.
Please.
Shall we go to the racetrack?
In this car.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Bali Sea is amazing!
The ocean is amazing!
It's so nice. You're here.
Ejima, over there.
Let's go see what's happening today.
What's that?
Let's go?
It's too bad you couldn't make the course.
It's a real shame.
I was looking forward to it.
I don't know what I'll do.
You're a candy girl too, right, Thomas?
I'm sure you are.
I'm sure it's going to rain, but it's going to rain a lot after this.
But it's going to rain a lot later.
It's going to rain at the festival.
It was raining so hard that it was raining in that area only during our time.
It was a festival called "Knights of the Expo".
But there...
I was wearing a sailor suit with a long skirt.
And the rain soaked it all up.
I was white as a sheet.
When it was over, I could squeeze out about a kilo of water.
It was heavy, wasn't it?
That was a tough performance.
That's amazing.
Will it rain at the festival?
It's going to rain.
It rains a lot.
I see.
Is there anyone else besides you, Tomami?
I don't know.
I think it's me. I think it's perfect. When I was in the first grade of junior high school.
I felt like I had the power of rain in me when I was in the first year of junior high school.
From the entrance ceremony in the first year of middle school to the graduation ceremony in the third year of high school, almost every event was rained out.
I didn't think it would be me because I've been talking about it.
I thought I was in a rainy school year, but after I graduated, I started playing in a band, and every time we had an event, it rained.
So it was just me! That's amazing!
That's a possibility, right?
By the way, I heard from Sodan that Tobomi is the parent of the ocean in this show.
I heard from Mr. Sodan
I saw a picture on your instagram
and wrote something like, "Please make a special golf show because I went with musician friends.
I tagged it with "special" and told them to definitely read it.
I'm sure it didn't become a project right away, but that comment was the catalyst for the idea of a special golf show.
But I don't even play golf that much.
I went with a musician friend of mine and we were so excited that I asked him to make it a special, but he said, "I don't even go once a year.
I haven't been to one in a year.
It must be nerve-wracking to sing and perform in front of so many people.
Not at all. I do too.
I still get nervous. I bet you were nervous at the beginning.
I didn't know what I was doing at first.
There was nothing to be afraid of.
I didn't know if I was doing well or not.
I was just like...
I was like, "Wow!
I did the double encore on my own.
On your own?
After the encore, I said I didn't want to buy it yet, so I wanted to sing one more song.
Wow!
Now that I think about it...
If I were a member of the staff, I'd be like, "Oh my God!
Now I'm like, "Where's the sound going to go?
And we have to set up the lights.
I didn't think about that.
I've never thought about that before.
Even if there's a gallery or something, it's still a relatively quiet place.
You have to give a concentrated performance.
In a scene.
I can't imagine
I can't imagine what it would be like to be seen in such a scene.
If you are really competing for the championship
I don't even feel like I'm being watched anymore.
It's like you're in your own world, your own zone.
You don't even hear the sounds around you anymore.
It's the opposite of concentration.
That's for sure.
I'm actually type A, but I've never been told I'm type A.
What do they call you?
Type O or B.
But blood type horoscopes say that A and B aren't compatible.
That's true. That's not true at all.
Maybe it doesn't matter. We're all friends.
Yay!
What's the blood type of the person you fall in love with?
The same?
I've only dated AB and O types.
I've never been with an A or a B.
I see.
But I feel more comfortable with someone who's strong.
I'm really naive.
I see.
I've only done bungees since I was a teenager.
I don't know anything about the world.
I'm aware that I probably don't know much about the world, so I'd be more comfortable with someone who knows a lot of things.
I also want someone who is kind and forgives me.
I understand! I understand!
She's the most maidenly person!
If you forget something and say, "Oh, no, I brought it...", she's like, "Oh, no, I brought it...".
I know!
That's the best!
Oh, this one!
Is this America? Is this America?
America? Is this California?
Is this California? Is this California?
We're here!
Thank you so much!
Wow!
Wow, it's wine, but it's amazing!
Here we go!
Stylish!
Very stylish!
That's nice.
Wow, where'd you get that?
Here we are!
I can't believe the rain's coming.
Oh, my God.
We can't go round the garden.
It's raining sideways.
I wish I could have gone with the windchill.
Too bad.
It's a little cold.
It's cold.
I didn't know there was a place that looked so good.
It looks really good.
It's so cute!
I'd like to see a lot of professional stuff first.
Can I see them?
Yes, please.
Yes, I'll try my best.
There are games like that.
It's like a game where you have to hit a certain distance as accurately as you can.
I'm a little nervous, too.
Let's watch and learn.
Okay, I'll set it up.
Okay, we'll start here.
That's how we'll start.
For now, we're going to use a screwdriver.
Can you fit a screwdriver this wide?
Yeah.
So, this is the guy that I saw, and he said that the weather on this thing is really bad, and he's looking at it, right?
So if there's wind, he knows it's going to turn.
If it's a guest, it won't fly.
Okay, let's get started. Please.
How far are you going?
Look out! Just barely... just barely.
Just in time. Just in time, really.
212? Just barely.
Look out! Next 103 yards.
I have to get to the stash.
It's like a game where you have to get inside the
Is that what this is about? There's no room at all!
I'm serious. It's pretty nerve-wracking.
Here.
Wait, please come in.
Okay.
And right in the middle.
This game is fun, isn't it?
I didn't know this existed.
I had used a stop tracer before, but...
I didn't know there was such a game.
Wow!
This one's off. This one's off.
Is it off?
I know, I know, I know, I know.
Oh, just barely.
Oh, my God.
Why is the rain coming like this?
It's raining like crazy.
I feel like it's going to fly away.
Oh my God, I'm terrible at this.
But I'll make an excuse.
The wind...
You're right.
Rupture!
Oh, my God, that's so cool!
That's cool.
I got it.
It's a good opportunity to know your distance.
It's a good chance to know how far away you are.
I'm so excited!
Wait, wait, wait!
Straight ahead!
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!